

Arvind Singh Rajput



OBJECTIVE

Security professional with having an experience of more than 11 years of in the Domain of Physical Security, command center operations, visitor management, material management, VIP Management, Theft Investigation for theft & pilferage. Vigilance am looking For the Opportunity in security position where am I can use my Skills in devolving strategies and leading a team



ADDRESS

A/40 maipalnagar opp. Chandkheda railway station cahndkheda Ahmedabad



PHONE 9724813126



EMAIL

Arvind8568@gmail.co



HOBBIES

Watching Movie

Travelling

Reading Novel

Listening Music

EXPERIENCE

Security Officer (MSF Payroll)

- Adani Corporate House (Nov 2019 To Present) Security Supervisor (ISS Security)
- Adani Shantigram Township (2016 to 2019) Security Supervisor (Pioneer Security)
- Adani House Navarangpura (2013 To 2016) Security Supervisor (ISS Security)
- Tata Consultancy Service (March 2010 To June 2012)

EDUCATION

BA Gujarat University (2007) HSC Gujarat Board (2004) SSC Gujarat Board (2002)

SKILLS -

Fire Fighting
Material Management
Traffic Safety management
UVSS
CCTV
Access Control
VIP Movement
Emergency Response
Mock drill
Investigation
Deployment
Security Self Defense

CERTIFICATE

- Best Security Supervisor certificate award with ADANI Group.
- Best Security Supervisor certificate award POINEER Group.
- Fire Training (Adani Corporate House)
- Certificate Of Appreciation For Adani Vidiya Mandir Covid Center (2021)

COMPUTER SKIILS

Basic Computer Knowledge Outlook MS Office

DECLARATION:

I hereby declare that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

ARVIND SINGH RAJPUT

